<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<posts>
  <row Id="4" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="7" CreationDate="2008-07-31T21:42:52.667" Score="379" ViewCount="25677" Body="&lt;p&gt;I want to use a track-bar to change a form's opacity.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is my code:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;decimal trans = trackBar1.Value / 5000;&#xA;this.Opacity = trans;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When I try to build it, I get this error:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Cannot implicitly convert type 'decimal' to 'double'.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I tried making &lt;code&gt;trans&lt;/code&gt; a &lt;code&gt;double&lt;/code&gt;, but then the control doesn't work. This code has worked fine for me in VB.NET in the past. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="8" LastEditorUserId="5455605" LastEditorDisplayName="Rich B" LastEditDate="2015-12-23T21:34:28.557" LastActivityDate="2015-12-23T21:34:28.557" Title="When setting a form's opacity should I use a decimal or double?" Tags="&lt;c#&gt;&lt;winforms&gt;&lt;type-conversion&gt;&lt;decimal&gt;&lt;opacity&gt;" AnswerCount="13" CommentCount="1" FavoriteCount="30" CommunityOwnedDate="2012-10-31T16:42:47.213" />
  <row Id="6" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="31" CreationDate="2008-07-31T22:08:08.620" Score="168" ViewCount="12524" Body="&lt;p&gt;I have an absolutely positioned &lt;code&gt;div&lt;/code&gt; containing several children, one of which is a relatively positioned &lt;code&gt;div&lt;/code&gt;. When I use a &lt;strong&gt;percentage-based width&lt;/strong&gt; on the child &lt;code&gt;div&lt;/code&gt;, it collapses to &lt;code&gt;0&lt;/code&gt; width on IE7, but not on Firefox or Safari. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If I use &lt;strong&gt;pixel width&lt;/strong&gt;, it works. If the parent is relatively positioned, the percentage width on the child works. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Is there something I'm missing here? &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Is there an easy fix for this besides the &lt;em&gt;pixel-based width&lt;/em&gt; on the&#xA;child? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Is there an area of the &lt;code&gt;CSS&lt;/code&gt; specification that covers this?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="9" LastEditorUserId="5104596" LastEditorDisplayName="Rich B" LastEditDate="2015-12-26T06:11:47.633" LastActivityDate="2015-12-26T06:11:47.633" Title="Percentage width child element in absolutely positioned parent on IE7" Tags="&lt;html&gt;&lt;css&gt;&lt;css3&gt;&lt;internet-explorer-7&gt;" AnswerCount="5" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="7" />
  <row Id="474039" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="473617" CreationDate="2009-01-23T18:56:07.390" Score="14" Body="&lt;p&gt;Matt,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I would say that your shop is writing procedural code. I want to make clear that there is nothing wrong with that many large systems (including many I have worked on) have been written using procedural code. There is a time and place for it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now procedural code has no place in a domain model. If you want to use a more procedural style that is fine but use it with something like a Table Module or an Active Record pattern. It is not the lack of OO that I am considering to be so destructive in the guidance but the use of a domain model with procedural logic. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This causes one to spend a large amount of resources building the domain layer (impedance mismatch, thought process time to build aggregates, isolation, ubiquitous language etc) without receiving any of the benefits that the domain layer (generally maintainability) would otherwise provide. In other words while you may meet your functional requirements just fine you end up spending a large amount of your budget with almost no return.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now to come back to what &quot;is behavior&quot; I would like to focus on the question from an Object Oriented as opposed to a &quot;Domain Driven Design&quot; viewpoint. An object will generally encapsulate some state and will generally expose some behaviors. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;quick reiteration: encapsulate state, expose behavior&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So what behaviors should an object have? Put simply it should be the behaviors that operate upon the state it is encapsulating. In an ideal behavioral OO world the state would never be exposed from the object only behaviors. Put tactically into code if we start seeing code like:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;Customer c = GetCustomerFromRepository();&#xA;c.Status = CustomerStatuses.Deleted;&#xA;c.LastUpdated = DateTime.Now;&#xA;c.UpdatedBy = GetCurrentUser();&#xA;CustomerRepository.Save(c);&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We have a SRP violation ... This code is code that should be a behavior of the customer object because the &quot;Responsibility&quot; of the customer object is to.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Encapsulate state about a customer and expose behaviors.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As such we can see that we would be better off having a Customer.Delete() method. (yes this is a bad example I know ...)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now we would also get to this by using TDD. It is much easier for us to deal in tests with the seam that the behavior provides than the seams where all of the state is exposed. The reason for this is that I don't need to duplicate the logic in my tests. The client code doesn't &lt;em&gt;care&lt;/em&gt; how a delete works ... it only cares that the customer exposes the behavior. As such in our tests instead of asserting that c.State == CustomerStates.Deleted and c.UpdatedBy==GetCurrentUser() etc etc we would simply assert that the delete method was called on the customer seam by using a mock.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now to come back to the title. The amount of logic that should be in a business object is the amount of logic that falls under its responsibility of encapsulating its state. Sometimes this is alot, sometimes its not. There are places where you want to use services as well ... a good example would be coordinating the interaction between many domain objects for a given behavior but even here the service should be calling &lt;em&gt;behaviors&lt;/em&gt; on the domain objects.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Does this help to clarify things a bit?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Greg&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="58396" OwnerDisplayName="Greg Young" LastEditorUserId="1116" LastEditorDisplayName="Greg Young" LastEditDate="2009-08-27T14:51:36.077" LastActivityDate="2009-08-27T14:51:36.077" CommentCount="6" />
  <row Id="474040" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="463105" CreationDate="2009-01-23T18:56:12.990" Score="16" Body="&lt;p&gt;Based on dsimcha's code, I've implemented a more generic version that fits well into the framework we use (SeqAn). Actually, porting the code was completely straightforward. Only afterwards did I find that there &lt;em&gt;are&lt;/em&gt; actually publications concerning this very topic. The great thing is: they basically say the same as you guys. A paper by Andersson and Nilsson on &lt;a href=&quot;http://user.it.uu.se/~arnea/ps/radimpl.pdf&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Implementing Radixsort&lt;/a&gt; is definitely worth the read. If you happen to know German, be sure to also read David Weese's &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.inf.fu-berlin.de/inst/ag-bio/FILES/ROOT/Teaching/Theses/Master/2006_finished//thesis_weese.pdf&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;diploma thesis&lt;/a&gt; where he implements a generic substring index. Most of the thesis is devoted to a detailed analysis of the cost of building the index, considering secondary memory and extremely large files. The results of his work have actually been implemented in SeqAn, only not in those parts where i needed it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Just for fun, here's the code I've written (I don't think anyone not using SeqAn will have any use for it). Notice that it still doesn't consider radixes greater 4. I expect that this would have a huge impact on performance but unfortunately I simply don't have the time right now to implement this.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The code performs more than twice as fast as Introsort for short strings. The break-even point is at a length of about 12–13. The type of string (e.g. whether it has 4, 5, or 16 different values) is comparatively unimportant. Sorting &gt; 6,000,000 DNA reads from chromosome 2 of the human genome takes just over 2 seconds on my PC. Just for the record, that's &lt;em&gt;fast&lt;/em&gt;! Especially considering that I don't use SIMD or any other hardware acceleration. Furthermore, valgrind shows me that the main bottleneck is &lt;code&gt;operator new&lt;/code&gt; in the string assignments. It gets called about 65,000,000 times – ten times for each string! This is a dead giveaway that &lt;code&gt;swap&lt;/code&gt; could be optimized for these strings: instead of making copies, it could just swap all characters. I didn't try this but I'm convinced that it would make a hell of a difference. And, just to say it again, in case someone wasn't listening: &lt;em&gt;the radix size has nearly no influence on runtime&lt;/em&gt; – which means that I should &lt;em&gt;definitely&lt;/em&gt; try to implement the suggestion made by FryGuy, Stephan and EvilTeach.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ah yes, by the way: &lt;strong&gt;cache locality &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; a noticeable factor&lt;/strong&gt;: Starting at 1M strings, the runtime no longer increases linearly. However, this could be fixed quite easily: I use insertion sort for small subsets (&amp;lt;= 20 strings) – instead of mergesort as suggested by the random hacker. Apparently, this performs even better than mergesort for such small lists (see the first paper I linked).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;namespace seqan {&#xA;&#xA;template &amp;lt;typename It, typename F, typename T&amp;gt;&#xA;inline void prescan(It front, It back, F op, T const&amp;amp; id) {&#xA;    using namespace std;&#xA;    if (front == back) return;&#xA;    typename iterator_traits&amp;lt;It&amp;gt;::value_type accu = *front;&#xA;    *front++ = id;&#xA;    for (; front != back; ++front) {&#xA;        swap(*front, accu);&#xA;        accu = op(accu, *front);&#xA;    }&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;template &amp;lt;typename TIter, typename TSize, unsigned int RADIX&amp;gt;&#xA;inline void radix_permute(TIter front, TIter back, TSize (&amp;amp; bounds)[RADIX], TSize base) {&#xA;    for (TIter i = front; i != back; ++i)&#xA;        ++bounds[static_cast&amp;lt;unsigned int&amp;gt;((*i)[base])];&#xA;&#xA;    TSize fronts[RADIX];&#xA;&#xA;    std::copy(bounds, bounds + RADIX, fronts);&#xA;    prescan(fronts, fronts + RADIX, std::plus&amp;lt;TSize&amp;gt;(), 0);&#xA;    std::transform(bounds, bounds + RADIX, fronts, bounds, plus&amp;lt;TSize&amp;gt;());&#xA;&#xA;    TSize active_base = 0;&#xA;&#xA;    for (TIter i = front; i != back; ) {&#xA;        if (active_base == RADIX - 1)&#xA;            return;&#xA;        while (fronts[active_base] &amp;gt;= bounds[active_base])&#xA;            if (++active_base == RADIX - 1)&#xA;                return;&#xA;        TSize current_base = static_cast&amp;lt;unsigned int&amp;gt;((*i)[base]);&#xA;        if (current_base &amp;lt;= active_base)&#xA;            ++i;&#xA;        else&#xA;            std::iter_swap(i, front + fronts[current_base]);&#xA;        ++fronts[current_base];&#xA;    }&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;template &amp;lt;typename TIter, typename TSize&amp;gt;&#xA;inline void insertion_sort(TIter front, TIter back, TSize base) {&#xA;    typedef typename Value&amp;lt;TIter&amp;gt;::Type T;&#xA;    struct {&#xA;        TSize base, len;&#xA;        bool operator ()(T const&amp;amp; a, T const&amp;amp; b) {&#xA;            for (TSize i = base; i &amp;lt; len; ++i)&#xA;                if (a[i] &amp;lt; b[i]) return true;&#xA;                else if (a[i] &amp;gt; b[i]) return false;&#xA;            return false;&#xA;        }&#xA;    } cmp = { base, length(*front) }; // No closures yet. :-(&#xA;&#xA;    for (TIter i = front + 1; i != back; ++i) {&#xA;        T value = *i;&#xA;        TIter j = i;&#xA;        for ( ; j != front &amp;amp;&amp;amp; cmp(value, *(j - 1)); --j)&#xA;            *j = *(j - 1);&#xA;        if (j != i)&#xA;            *j = value;&#xA;    }&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;template &amp;lt;typename TIter, typename TSize, unsigned int RADIX&amp;gt;&#xA;inline void radix(TIter top, TIter front, TIter back, TSize base, TSize (&amp;amp; parent_bounds)[RADIX], TSize next) {&#xA;    if (back - front &amp;gt; 20) {&#xA;        TSize bounds[RADIX] = { 0 };&#xA;        radix_permute(front, back, bounds, base);&#xA;&#xA;        // Sort current bucket recursively by suffix.&#xA;        if (base &amp;lt; length(*front) - 1)&#xA;            radix(front, front, front + bounds[0], base + 1, bounds, static_cast&amp;lt;TSize&amp;gt;(0));&#xA;    }&#xA;    else if (back - front &amp;gt; 1)&#xA;        insertion_sort(front, back, base);&#xA;&#xA;    // Sort next buckets on same level recursively.&#xA;    if (next == RADIX - 1) return;&#xA;    radix(top, top + parent_bounds[next], top + parent_bounds[next + 1], base, parent_bounds, next + 1);&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;template &amp;lt;typename TIter&amp;gt;&#xA;inline void radix_sort(TIter front, TIter back) {&#xA;    typedef typename Container&amp;lt;TIter&amp;gt;::Type TStringSet;&#xA;    typedef typename Value&amp;lt;TStringSet&amp;gt;::Type TString;&#xA;    typedef typename Value&amp;lt;TString&amp;gt;::Type TChar;&#xA;    typedef typename Size&amp;lt;TStringSet&amp;gt;::Type TSize;&#xA;&#xA;    TSize const RADIX = ValueSize&amp;lt;TChar&amp;gt;::VALUE;&#xA;    TSize bounds[RADIX];&#xA;&#xA;    radix(front, front, back, static_cast&amp;lt;TSize&amp;gt;(0), bounds, RADIX - 1);&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;} // namespace seqan&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1968" OwnerDisplayName="Konrad Rudolph" LastEditorUserId="1968" LastEditDate="2014-06-17T09:31:52.633" LastActivityDate="2014-06-17T09:31:52.633" CommentCount="21" />
  <row Id="474041" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="473937" CreationDate="2009-01-23T18:56:20.027" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;Check out the documentation here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://pycurl.sourceforge.net/doc/callbacks.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;http://pycurl.sourceforge.net/doc/callbacks.html&lt;/a&gt; for callbacks. Best of luck!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="58114" OwnerDisplayName="Andy Mikula" LastActivityDate="2009-01-23T18:56:20.027" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="474042" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="360956" CreationDate="2009-01-23T18:56:37.590" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;Something that everyone wants to know... How does it affect them?  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="41713" LastActivityDate="2009-01-23T18:56:37.590" CommentCount="0" CommunityOwnedDate="2009-01-23T18:56:37.577" />
  <row Id="474043" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="474007" CreationDate="2009-01-23T18:57:07.230" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;You can use an unsigned char to read the float byte by byte into the integer array:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;unsigned int bits[sizeof (float) * CHAR_BIT];&#xA;unsigned char const *c = static_cast&amp;lt;unsigned char const*&amp;gt;(&#xA;    static_cast&amp;lt;void const*&amp;gt;(&amp;amp;my_float)&#xA;);&#xA;&#xA;for(size_t i = 0; i &amp;lt; sizeof(float) * CHAR_BIT; i++) {&#xA;    int bitnr = i % CHAR_BIT;&#xA;    bits[i] = (*c &amp;gt;&amp;gt; bitnr) &amp;amp; 1;&#xA;    if(bitnr == CHAR_BIT-1)&#xA;        c++;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;// the bits are now stored in &quot;bits&quot;. one bit in one integer.&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By the way, if you just want to compare the bits (as you comment on another answer) use &lt;code&gt;memcmp&lt;/code&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;memcmp(&amp;amp;float1, &amp;amp;float2, sizeof (float));&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="34509" OwnerDisplayName="litb" LastEditorUserId="34509" LastEditorDisplayName="litb" LastEditDate="2009-01-23T19:57:13.443" LastActivityDate="2009-01-23T19:57:13.443" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="474044" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2009-01-23T18:57:20.147" Score="1" ViewCount="1227" Body="&lt;p&gt;I have a one-to-many relationship. I would like to construct this query:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Give me all the parents that have only one child and for this child child.Type=X&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Since I 'm learning, please show me the query with the Criteria API and with HQL. Thanks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And btw, is there any automatic way to know what HQL is identical to a criteria expression ?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It seems I found how to do it in HQL:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;@&quot;select Parent&#xA;    from Parent parent&#xA;        join parent.Children ch&#xA;        where (ch.Type = :chType) and&#xA;              (select count(*) from parent.Children) = 1&quot;)&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But is it well done? How is the performance? I have the intuition that the count(*) is not well placed...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="29244" OwnerDisplayName="Nicolas Cadilhac" LastEditorUserId="29244" LastEditorDisplayName="Nicolas Cadilhac" LastEditDate="2009-01-26T01:49:05.470" LastActivityDate="2009-01-26T01:49:05.453" Title="How to construct this NHibernate query" Tags="&lt;nhibernate&gt;&lt;hql&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="474045" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="473979" CreationDate="2009-01-23T18:57:35.560" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'd suggest using an external tool for it - here's one way with perl:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;$(echo &quot;$variable&quot; | perl -e 'print &quot;edited:&quot;; while (&amp;lt;&amp;gt;) { while (/--- (\S+)/g) { print &quot; $1&quot;; } }')&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I'm sure it can be done more elegantly, but I can't think of a way right now that wouldn't take a more substantial program.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="56541" OwnerDisplayName="David" LastActivityDate="2009-01-23T18:57:35.560" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="474046" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="474187" CreationDate="2009-01-23T18:57:50.100" Score="0" ViewCount="388" Body="&lt;p&gt;On a very important Windows server we use a scheduled task set up by the mysqladmin utility to back up our critical data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I'd like to use the simpler mysqldump command, but I want to ensure that the output is the same. Presumably mysqladmin and mysqldump both share a common core dumping component, so for any given setting in mysqladmin I ought to be able to find a configuration for mysqldump which produce the &lt;strong&gt;exact same output&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But how?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At the moment I am resorting to trial &amp;amp; error - but is there a better way to do it? &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="46411" OwnerDisplayName="Salim Fadhley" LastActivityDate="2009-01-23T19:36:30.320" Title="How to get the exact same output from mysqldump as mysqladmin/backup" Tags="&lt;mysql&gt;&lt;mysqldump&gt;&lt;mysqladministrator&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="474047" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="474410" CreationDate="2009-01-23T18:57:52.423" Score="2" ViewCount="2769" Body="&lt;p&gt;I have a windows service that has a custom configuration section.  In the configSectionHandler class I am using attributes on the properties to validate the settings like this:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;    //ProcessingSleepTime Property&#xA;    [ConfigurationProperty(&quot;ProcessingSleepTime&quot;, DefaultValue = 1000, IsRequired = false)]&#xA;    [IntegerValidator(MinValue = 5, MaxValue = 60000)]&#xA;    public Int32 ProcessingSleepTime&#xA;    {&#xA;        get&#xA;        {&#xA;            if (this[&quot;ProcessingSleepTime&quot;] == null)&#xA;                return 100;&#xA;&#xA;            return (Int32)this[&quot;ProcessingSleepTime&quot;];&#xA;        }&#xA;        set&#xA;        {&#xA;            this[&quot;ProcessingSleepTime&quot;] = value;&#xA;        }&#xA;    }&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If a value in the configuration file fails validation, a ConfigurationErrorsException is thrown.  In a windows service this happens as it is trying to start and it's really ugly (it offers to launch the debugger).  How can I gracefully handle this error?  I tried wrapping the OnStart method in a try/catch but it had no effect.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thanks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="35165" OwnerDisplayName="Rick" LastActivityDate="2009-01-23T22:17:47.247" Title="How/Where to handle ConfigurationErrorsException in a windows service?" Tags="&lt;c#&gt;&lt;windows-services&gt;&lt;configuration-files&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="3" />
  <row Id="474049" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="473998" CreationDate="2009-01-23T18:58:40.550" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;I would use a RegEx and count the number of occurrences. You can do this in a myriad of languages, even a simple shell script would do it, e.g. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;grep -E &quot;.*ERROR.*\n&quot; logfile | wc -l&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="58142" OwnerDisplayName="Spikolynn" LastActivityDate="2009-01-23T18:58:40.550" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="474050" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="478833" CreationDate="2009-01-23T18:58:40.583" Score="8" ViewCount="6917" Body="&lt;p&gt;I've run into a snag with a ADO.NET Entity Framework model and a ADO.NET Data Service that is making it available.  The model and data service are compiling without any problems or warnings when they come out of source control.  However when I run the service I get the following error:&#xA;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i42.tinypic.com/5lds8p.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Request Error - The server encountered an error processing the request.  See server logs for more details.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately there are no server logs (that I am aware of) since this is VS 2008 web dev server and there really isn't any code to debug.....  Through some trial and error it would appear that the generated code (model.Designer.cs) is out of date in some manner.  If I perform some trivial update to the EDM that forces it to regenerate the code file, when I rerun the service it works just fine.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I've tried to delete the model.designer.cs file in the hopes that during the build the project/entity builder would detect the missing file and regenerate it for me.  That didn't happen..... Does anyone know how to force this code to be regenerated?  (It would also make me a bit happier about not having to keep generated code under source control.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thanks&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="52136" OwnerDisplayName="confusedGeek" LastActivityDate="2009-01-26T04:23:25.020" Title="How to force ADO.NET Entity Framework to regenerate code?" Tags="&lt;entity-framework&gt;&lt;wcf-data-services&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="1" />
  <row Id="474051" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="473998" CreationDate="2009-01-23T18:59:07.603" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;If you know/like .NET, the &lt;a href=&quot;http://msmvps.com/blogs/jon_skeet/archive/2008/01/04/quot-push-quot-linq-revisited-next-attempt-at-an-explanation.aspx&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Push LINQ&lt;/a&gt; framework that Marc Gravell and I developed would be an ideal candidate for this. Basically, you set up all the aggregation you want (grouping, summing etc) beforehand, and &quot;push&quot; the logfile through it, then ask for the results at the end. This would let you do everything with near-constant memory consumption and a single pass through the data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let me know if you want more details.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22656" OwnerDisplayName="Jon Skeet" LastActivityDate="2009-01-23T18:59:07.603" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="474052" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="402334" CreationDate="2009-01-23T18:59:19.957" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;Imo, Spring.Net and NHibernate go hand in hand: If you master the learning curve you will be very pleased when Spring is used for (almost transparent) &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.springframework.net/doc-latest/reference/html/orm.html#orm-hibernate&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;transaction handling&lt;/a&gt; for NHibernate, Dependency Injection as well as Db:Provider handling.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="27083" OwnerDisplayName="tobsen" LastActivityDate="2009-01-23T18:59:19.957" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="474053" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="225471" CreationDate="2009-01-23T18:59:30.800" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;The key is to use two columns: &lt;code&gt;canonical_text&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;original_text&lt;/code&gt;.  Use &lt;code&gt;original_text&lt;/code&gt; for display and &lt;code&gt;canonical_text&lt;/code&gt; for searches.  That way, if a user searches for &quot;Visual Cafe,&quot; she sees the &quot;Visual Café&quot; result.  If she &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; wants a different item called &quot;Visual Cafe,&quot; it can be saved separately.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To get the characters in a Ruby 1.8 source file, do something like this:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;register_replacement([0x008A].pack('U'), 'S')&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1190" OwnerDisplayName="Gaius" LastActivityDate="2009-01-23T18:59:30.800" CommentCount="1" CommunityOwnedDate="2009-01-23T18:59:30.783" />
  <row Id="474054" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="473648" CreationDate="2009-01-23T19:00:17.163" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;Learning multiple languages eventually gives you the ability to see them more as dialects of the same language.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="7891" OwnerDisplayName="R.A" LastActivityDate="2009-01-23T19:00:17.163" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="474055" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="474069" CreationDate="2009-01-23T19:00:17.443" Score="1" ViewCount="2741" Body="&lt;p&gt;In Java you can read a file embedded inside a JAR-file by using the following code:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;String file = &quot;com/company/package/filename.txt&quot;;&#xA;InputStream is = ClassName.class.getClassLoader().getResourceAsStream(file);&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What is the C#/.NET equivalent of the above code - that is, how do I read a file I've embedded inside a DLL?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="58394" LastActivityDate="2009-01-23T19:04:29.650" Title="C# equivalent of getClassLoader().getResourceAsStream(...)" Tags="&lt;c#&gt;&lt;dll&gt;&lt;embedded-resource&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="1" CommunityOwnedDate="2009-01-23T19:00:17.427" />
  <row Id="474056" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="472724" CreationDate="2009-01-23T19:00:19.957" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;How safe depends on where the user is located. SQL Server Reporting Services was not intended to be opened up to the Internet, for instance. Neither was the SQL Server database engine, for that matter. You said there's a firewall between the web server and the SQL Server, but that's not an unusual configuration in internal networks nowadays. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The concern that might come up is one from the performance side, more than any other. By viewing the reports using SSRS, the report rendering will occur on the same server as your database engine. If the hardware isn't enough for both roles, you'll see performance issues. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="29084" OwnerDisplayName="K. Brian Kelley" LastActivityDate="2009-01-23T19:00:19.957" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="474057" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="474196" CreationDate="2009-01-23T19:01:17.083" Score="1" ViewCount="1036" Body="&lt;p&gt;Is there a way to initialize all elements of an array to a constant value through generics?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22769" OwnerDisplayName="Igor Zelaya" LastActivityDate="2009-01-23T20:09:52.403" Title="How to initialize an array through generics?" Tags="&lt;c#&gt;&lt;generics&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="1" />
  <row Id="474058" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="474007" CreationDate="2009-01-23T19:01:18.753" Score="13" Body="&lt;p&gt;Use union and bitset:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;#include &amp;lt;iostream&amp;gt;&#xA;#include &amp;lt;bitset&amp;gt;&#xA;&#xA;int main()&#xA;{&#xA;    union&#xA;    {&#xA;         float input;   // assumes sizeof(float) == sizeof(int)&#xA;         int   output;&#xA;    }    data;&#xA;&#xA;    data.input = 2.25125;&#xA;&#xA;    std::bitset&amp;lt;sizeof(float) * CHAR_BIT&amp;gt;   bits(data.output);&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;    std::cout &amp;lt;&amp;lt; bits &amp;lt;&amp;lt; std::endl;&#xA;&#xA;    // or&#xA;&#xA;    std::cout &amp;lt;&amp;lt; &quot;BIT 4: &quot; &amp;lt;&amp;lt; bits[4] &amp;lt;&amp;lt; std::endl;&#xA;    std::cout &amp;lt;&amp;lt; &quot;BIT 7: &quot; &amp;lt;&amp;lt; bits[7] &amp;lt;&amp;lt; std::endl;&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It may not be an array but you can access bits with [] operator as if you were using an array.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Output&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ ./bits&#xA;01000000000100000001010001111011&#xA;BIT 4: 1&#xA;BIT 7: 0&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="14065" OwnerDisplayName="Martin York" LastEditorUserId="14065" LastEditorDisplayName="Martin York" LastEditDate="2009-01-23T20:04:29.030" LastActivityDate="2009-01-23T20:04:29.030" CommentCount="5" />
  <row Id="474059" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="473998" CreationDate="2009-01-23T19:02:01.450" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;Here's a unix (or &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cygwin.com/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Cygwin&lt;/a&gt;) command-line way do this with:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;An &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.vectorsite.net/tsawk.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;AWK&lt;/a&gt; command (to parse out the 4th field, where your fields are separated by pipes &quot;|&quot;)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;A &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.grymoire.com/Unix/Sed.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;SED&lt;/a&gt; command to replace the transaction # ([584]) above to make grouping easier (with [tid])&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;sort and uniq to find and count duplicate lines:&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here is the command-line:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;awk &quot;FS=\&quot;^|\&quot;;{print $4}&quot; logfile.txt | sed -e &quot;s/\[[0-9]*\]/[tid]/g&quot; \&#xA;| sort | uniq -c | sort&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here's the output:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;   1  Biz.Dee: Logout Transaction [id] executed in [id] milliseconds&#xA;   1  Foo.Bar: Backend error&#xA;   1  Foo.Bar: InvalidUserException&#xA;   1  Foo.Com: Timeout error&#xA;   3  Foo.Bar: Login Transaction [id] executed in [id] milliseconds&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="43815" OwnerDisplayName="NicJ" LastActivityDate="2009-01-23T19:02:01.450" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="474060" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="348611" CreationDate="2009-01-23T19:02:49.310" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;I would suggest against Agile when developing a new air traffic control system.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22303" OwnerDisplayName="fallen888" LastActivityDate="2009-01-23T19:02:49.310" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="474061" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="471727" CreationDate="2009-01-23T19:03:01.727" Score="8" Body="&lt;p&gt;This is way less than ideal, and I hope someone has a better solution, but it works:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Build a simple App using dom4j:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;public static void main( final String[] args ) throws Exception {&#xA;	String text = FileUtils.readFileToString( new File( args[ 0 ] ) );&#xA;	OutputFormat format = OutputFormat.createPrettyPrint();&#xA;	format.setTrimText( false );&#xA;&#xA;	XMLWriter writer = new XMLWriter( System.out, format );&#xA;	writer.write( DocumentHelper.parseText( text ) );&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Create a runnable jar, (optional) batch script, and add as an external tool. Of course, you could try XMLTidy or some other command line XML formatter, but I have had better results with dom4j.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="27657" OwnerDisplayName="javamonkey79" LastActivityDate="2009-01-23T19:03:01.727" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="474062" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="471288" CreationDate="2009-01-23T19:03:20.713" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;MySQL is popular for open source languages (PHP, Java, etc).  For .NET systems, people go with SQL Server Express Edition - Which is free.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="11112" OwnerDisplayName="tsilb" LastActivityDate="2009-01-23T19:03:20.713" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="474063" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2009-01-23T19:03:22.540" Score="2" ViewCount="741" Body="&lt;p&gt;Which is the best way of validating an input passed to the function i.e. do you validate all input before proceeding some thing like&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;class A;&#xA;void fun(A* p)&#xA;{&#xA;  if(! p)&#xA;  {&#xA;    return;&#xA;  }&#xA;&#xA; B* pB = p-&amp;gt;getB();&#xA;  if(! pB)&#xA;  {&#xA;    return;&#xA;  }&#xA;&#xA;.......&#xA;&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Or do you write it like this:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;void fun(A* p)&#xA;{&#xA;  if(p)&#xA;  {&#xA;    B* pB = p-&amp;gt;getB();&#xA;    if(pB)&#xA;    {&#xA;      .....&#xA;    }&#xA;  }&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am asking this because, if I use the first style then I'll have multiple return statements in my code which many people say are bad (don't know why) and if I use the second style then there will be too many levels of nesting in my code.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="39742" OwnerDisplayName="Naveen" LastEditorUserId="50447" LastEditorDisplayName="Rowland Shaw" LastEditDate="2009-01-23T19:06:05.670" LastActivityDate="2009-01-24T00:32:42.047" Title="Coding style - Input validation" Tags="&lt;c++&gt;&lt;coding-style&gt;" AnswerCount="7" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="3" />
  <row Id="474065" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="474092" CreationDate="2009-01-23T19:03:46.657" Score="2" ViewCount="793" Body="&lt;p&gt;There's no strongly typed View() method to return an ActionResult. So, suppose I have &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;class Edit : ViewPage&amp;lt;Frob&amp;gt;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In my FrobController, I will do something like &quot;return View(&quot;Edit&quot;, someFrob);&quot;. There's no checking going on here, so I have to always manually synchronize the view and controller's use of it. This is suboptimal, and I'm not aware of any built-in fixes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I added this method to my controller base class:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;public ActionResult ViewPage&amp;lt;V, M&amp;gt;(V view, M model)&#xA;    where V : ViewPage&amp;lt;M&amp;gt;&#xA;    where M : class {&#xA;    return View(typeof(V).Name, model);&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Note: The reason I take a view&#xA;  object that's never used is because,&#xA;  AFAIK, there's no way to get C#'s type&#xA;  inference to work otherwise. If I&#xA;  removed the view parameter, I'd need&#xA;  to specify V explicitly, which also&#xA;  means specifying M explicitly too...&#xA;  sigh.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So now, I can do this:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;  return ViewPage(new Views.Frob.Edit(), myFrob);&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I'm specifying the exact view (no problem if it gets renamed), and myFrob is typechecked to be the right model type. The ugly side is that I new up a Edit. Alternatively, I could write:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;  return ViewPage((Views.Frob.Edit)null, myFrob);&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One downside is that the the model must be an exact match. So with a ViewPage&gt;, I cannot pass in a List. I thought this might work:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;    public ActionResult ViewPage&amp;lt;V, M, T&amp;gt;(V view, T model)&#xA;        where V : ViewPage&amp;lt;M&amp;gt;&#xA;        where M : class &#xA;        where T : M {&#xA;        return View(typeof(V).Name, model);&#xA;    }&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But C#'s type inference can't figure it out. The other potential problem is that the name of the view type might not be the right name, as I think it can be overridden by attributes. But that's an easy fix if I run into it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Questions:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;How can I make this syntax cleaner?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;What downsides am I missing here?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Edit: With respect to the Controller knowing about the View, it only slightly does. The only thing it gets from the view is the Type, for which it grabs the name. So that's equivalent to passing in the string name. And the strongly typed model, which must match or it'll fail. So it doesn't really know too much about the View -- its just a trick to get the compiler to catch errors.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="27012" OwnerDisplayName="MichaelGG" LastEditorUserId="27012" LastEditorDisplayName="MichaelGG" LastEditDate="2009-01-23T20:33:17.520" LastActivityDate="2009-08-08T14:00:03.213" Title="Strongly typing ASP.NET Controller.View() method for model type" Tags="&lt;c#&gt;&lt;asp.net-mvc&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="474066" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="465180" CreationDate="2009-01-23T19:03:58.870" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;If you're on SQL Server 2005 or 2008, the best answer is one that's already been given, and that's DDL triggers. A properly written DDL trigger will stop even someone who has sysadmin rights from performing any sort of DDL operation.  A sysadmin can disable a trigger to perform work, or the trigger can be written to allow certain people to perform work, so you still have the option to make modifications as required. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you're on SQL Server 2000 (or below), your only recourse is to check security permissions for each login/user. Ultimately this is something that needs to be done even if you're on SQL Server 2005 or 2008, but there isn't a shortcut in the previous versions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="29084" OwnerDisplayName="K. Brian Kelley" LastActivityDate="2009-01-23T19:03:58.870" CommentCount="0" />
</posts>
